### Shayon Maramkhah

Stamford, CT 06903 | (475) 228-9171 | maramkhah1@gmail.com

## **Information Technology**

Highly motivated Information Technologist with experience in virtual machines and programming. Interested in developing strong connections with corporations in the IT field. Strong networking skills and the ability to adapt to the changing landscape of information technology.

### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

Quality Control, Software Application

Troubleshooting, programming, Help Desk, Customer Service.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Software: VMware, Virtualbox, Docker Hardware: Ardunio, switches, routers, PC's Operating Systems: Linux, Windows, MacOS

### **EDUCATION**

DeVry University

Online

## **Certification, Information Technology Essentials**

Relevant Coursework:

- Fundamentals of Information Technology
- Introduction to Technology and Information
- Introduction to Digital Devices

DeVry University - Keller Graduate School of Management

January 2024 - Present

Certificate: Information Technology Essentials

Western Connecticut State University - Bachelor of Arts

January 2016 - December 2021 Major: Applied Computing.

### **EXPERIENCE**

**Kubtec Medical Imaging** 

Field Service Technician

- Traveling to medical centers for machine maintenance
- Using OSI model for network troubleshooting

Movia Robotics Bristol

**Programming Internship** 

- Quality Control
- Android Studio
- Java Programing

Bristol, CT

June 2021 - December 2021

Stratford, CT

December 2020 - December 2020